# **Andriy Nasinnyk**

Ukraine, Kiev

phone: (098) 628 44 14

skype: nas\_ua

email: andriy.nas@gmail.com

linkedin: http://ua.linkedin.com/in/andriynas

github: <a href="https://github.com/Nas1k">https://github.com/Nas1k</a>

### **Summary**

I am PHP Software Engineer. I have more than 3 years experience working on projects with different complexity. I have experience in PHP, MySQL, SOAP, Cloud Computing, HTML/CSS, JavaScript and other technologies. I have worked on Linux platform and also am able to configure/administer software on this platform. I have experience with other tools like control version system, continues integration, bug trackers. I used work by agile methodology like Scrum, XP etc.

### **Skills**

### **Architect:**

OOP/OOD, DDD, TDD, Design Patterns, Enterprise Patterns, UML

#### PHP:

- Version: 4, 5, 5.3, 5.4

- Framework: Zend Framework, Code-Igniter, Symfony2

- ORM: Doctrine, Zend Db

- CMS/CMF/E-Commerce: Magento, Joomla, X-Cart, osCommerce, etc

- Tools: Phing, PHPUnit/Selenium, PHPDocumentator, xdebug, PHPCodeSniffer, PHPMD

- Extensios: cURL, mcrypt, tidy, POP3, APC

### JavaScript:

- Framework: JQuery, ExtJS

#### **Databases:**

- RDBS: MySQL (EAV, Adjacency List, Path Enumeration, Nested Set)

- Document-oriented: MongoDB (small experience)

### **Administration:**

- OS: CentOS, RedHat, Debian based

- Virtualization: OpenVZ, KVM, VirtualBox

### **Search Technologies:**

- Apache Solr

#### **Additional:**

- Control Version System: Git, Subversion, SourceSafe

- IDE: PHPStorm, NetBeans, Eclipse PDT

- Other Technologies: HTML, XML/XPath, SOAP, CSS, GetText, RegExp, AWS, Jenkins, JIRA

### **Agile Methodology:**

- Scrum, XP, Kanban

## **Experience**

### **PHP Developer at Magento**

January 2012 - Present

Project: <a href="http://www.magentgo.com">http://www.magentgo.com</a>

Technologies: PHP, JavaScript, Zend Framework, MongoDB, jQuery, PHPUnit/Selenium, Git

**Description:** Magento Go is software as a service for e-commerce platform Magento.

Role: PHP Developer

### PHP Engineer at MalkosUA

February 2011 - January 2012

Project: http://www.recyclebank.com

Technologies: PHP, JavaScript, MySQL, Magento, jQuery, Apache Solr, SOAP, Git

Description: Recyclebank is a service that rewards people for taking everyday green actions with

discounts and deals from thousands of local and national businesses.

Role: PHP/JavaScript Developer

### **Developer at MagneticOne**

July 2009 - February 2011

**Project:** http://www.shopping-cart-migration.com

Technologies: PHP, JavaScript, MySQL, Zend Framework, ExtJS, jQuery, Amazon Web Services

Description: Cart2Cart is an online shopping cart migration service which helps you to move data

from your current shopping cart to better one automatically.

**Role:** PHP Developer

Project: <a href="http://www.yaware.com">http://www.yaware.com</a>

Technologies: PHP, MySQL, JavaScript, Zend Framework, Doctrine, jQuery, Amazon SQS, SOAP,

PHPUnit, Phing

**Description:** Yaware is an efficient fully automated system for tracking your employees working time.

Role: PHP/JavaScript Developer

#### Web developer at ABC Site

October 2008 - June 2009

### A senior specialist is on the computer systems and telecommunications at PrivatBank

March 2008 - October 2008

### Languages

Ukrainian (Native or bilingual proficiency) Russian (Full professional proficiency) English (Limited working proficiency)

## **Education**

### **National Technical University of Ternopil**

Specialist, Computing systems and networks, 2007 – 2010

### **Technical College of TNTU**

Junior Specialist, Computing systems and networks, 2003 – 2007